I've come to the conclusion that the
CIA, at the top levels of the CIA, they
they really love it when a new president
is elected and he has no background in
intelligence or foreign policy. Usually,
Donald Trump is a very unique figure in
this in this scenario. Very unusual. But
Barack Obama,
>> two years as a senator.
>> Check it out, folks. It's gonna be
interesting. You're about to see a
former CIA officer tell Tucker quite a
bit of crazy stuff about the
organizations and their operations and
how they relate to United States
presidents with a bit of Barack Hussein
Obama thrown into the mix. So without
further ado, we are we're going to get
right into it. But first, do me a big
favor here. Like our video, share it
around, and that way we can keep
bringing you all this great hard-hitting
content. As always, patriots, I'm your
real Darian and this is Resist the
Mainstream.
>> We're contacted either one of us.
>> So then 2008 rolls around, Bush leaves
after two terms, Obama gets elected
>> and he's very much the peace candidate.
He's for transparency.
>> Well, I like to say that it was Saint
Obama that came down from the heavens
>> into the into the White House returns.
>> That's right. And um but he's very much
a I mean I remember um in fact being on
uh on television saying you know he was
this wildeyed peace neck lefty guy.
>> Mhm. Oh no he wasn't.
>> Oh he wasn't. You know this is something
that I've puzzled over for a long time.
And I've come to the conclusion that the
CIA, at the top levels of the CIA, they
they really love it when a new president
is elected and he has no background in
intelligence or foreign policy. Usually
Donald Trump is a very unique figure in
this in this scenario. Very unusual. But
Barack Obama, two years as a senator,
two years as a senator, no experience in
foreign policy, no experience in
intelligence. The day after an election,
the director of the CIA authorizes a
president-elect to begin receiving a
PDB, a president's daily brief. And so
the day after the election, they go with
this this 16-page document marked at six
levels above top secret, and they say,
"Mr. president-elect. Wait till you see
the cool things we're doing all around
the world. And they've sucked him in.
They made him one of the guys. And every
day they were like, "Wait till you see
the update on what we told you
yesterday. It's incredible." And then we
get the the feedback at the CIA. Oh, the
president loved this. The president had
a follow-up question on that. Oh, the
president said, "Oh my god," when he
read this. Well, that's
>> almost psychologically profiling the
president.
>> Oh, I think I think that's exactly what
they do. And don't forget, they have an
entire staff of psychiatrists and
psychologists that do exactly that.
>> I mean, it's not surprising given that
the CIA provably has experimented with
weird things, including mind control.
This was revealed in Foya documents.
Just check out MK Ultra. Give that a
quick little Google search and read
about it on Wikipedia and maybe some
other sources if you're interested to
learn more. Now, as far as Donald Trump
goes, he famously did not like the CIA
at all. I suppose he had a bit of a
better intuition than some of the other
presidents. I mean, you can't blame the
guy. You know, he had to deal with a
lot. And more and more info on what the
CIA is is and what they've done to
specifically President Trump is still
coming out. Just take a look at this
briefing from March 2024. All right.
According to these documents here
drafted up by the House Judiciary
Committee, the CIA, particularly
President Obama CIA Director John
Brennan, actually worked to weaponize
the agency against the American people.
And they said very specifically that CIA
director Brendan identified 26 Trump
associates for the five eyes
intelligence line nations. These are the
United States, United Kingdom, Canada,
Australia, and New Zealand specifically
to target them into intelligence
operations and that he approved a plan
to request that foreign intelligence
agencies spy on people affiliated with
the Trump campaign. And they also say
that, you know, Russia played a big hand
in hurting the Democrats and helping
Trump win the election. And that's
something that Trump has repeatedly
rejected. In fact, Trump very famously
said, "There is nobody who feels
stronger about the intelligence agency
than Donald Trump." And you know, hey, I
can't blame the guy. He arguably has had
the most political weaponization against
him by government agencies of any
president in US history and at the very
least in our many of our lifetimes. That
much is fatly clear.
>> And so they use the tools
um that they have employed for decades
to subvert foreign governments to
subvert their own government.
>> Yes. But they smile while they're doing
it and they say, "No, no, we're just
trying to forge a good working
relationship with the president." In
fact, for a while in the '9s, they
didn't even call him the president. They
called him the first customer.
>> Swear to swear to God.
>> Is there I know we're getting farfield
and we will get back to your story, but
it it it doesn't sound like So, if you
look at the org chart, the president
controls CIA.
>> Yes.
>> But you're describing a a situation
where CIA kind of controls the
president.
>> You know, this is another problem. It's
that presidents come and go every four
years, every 8 years, but these these
CIA people, they're there for 25, 30, 35
years, they don't go anywhere. And so if
they don't like a president or if a
president orders them to do something
that they don't want to do, they just
wait because they know they can wait him
out and then he's not going to be
president anymore and they can continue
on with whatever plan the blob or the
deep state wants to implement. You know,
Russian President Vladimir Putin
actually said something very eerily
similar to this. Check it out.
forchech.
You know, like him or hate them, you
can't deny the undeniable and sad, scary
reality of that. It makes you question
sometimes. Is the founding father's
whole idea of self-governance, is that
actually being put into practice in our
current nation? Or is the illusion of
choice just that, nothing but an
illusion? You know, Donald Trump took a
lot of guff in his first term when he
used on a regular basis the term deep
state. And I argued from the very
beginning, it is a deep state. Maybe you
don't like the terminology. You don't
have to call it the deep state. You can
call it the federal bureaucracy. You can
call it the state. But the truth is that
it exists.
I I would say by definition, I mean, you
just described it, the president. And by
the way, the elected representatives who
are the instrument of the population
through which they control their
government um you know are perennial.
They come and go, but the people who
carry out those orders remain. So over
time they are the ones with the power,
right?
>> And then when they get caught, they
scramble. I remember Jane Harmon, she
was a congress congresswoman from uh
Venice, California. She was the
chairwoman of the House Intelligence
Committee during the Iraq war. And uh
she was briefed on the torture program.
Well, when I went public on the torture
program, reporters had questions. Well,
did Congress approve this? Of course,
Congress approved it and Congress
appropriated money for it. So, she's the
chairman and reporters went to her and
said, "Hey, what about this torture
program?" And she said, "I didn't know
anything about the torture program."
>> She's a liar.
>> She was lying. And I said, and I
remember saying it to the New York
Times, I said she was in the room when
it was briefed. A fun fact about Jane
Harmon that maybe you don't know. She
allegedly said that she wanted to go
ahead and lobby the DOJ to actually
reduce espionage charges on two people
who worked with Apac, the American
Israeli Political Action Committee. Why
did she want to do this? Of course, in
exchange for becoming the chair of the
House Intelligence Committee. I'm not
kidding. That is the allegation.
Like George Carlin once said, it's a big
club and you're not in it. Folks, thank
you for tuning in. Really appreciate it.
As always, if you haven't already, make
sure you comment below. Let us know what
you liked about the clip, what kind of
stuff you want to see in the future, and
hit that subscribe button. And that way,
we will see you again soon. And to those
who have subscribed, thank you so much.
We appreciate you.